in this tutorial we'll be going over how
在本教程中，我们将介绍如何
you can create this mountain range logo
你可以创建这个山脉标志
with the winding River using nothing but
随着蜿蜒的河流只用了
simple shapes in inkscape I should
Inkscape中的简单形状我应该
mention though that this tutorial is
尽管如此，请注意本教程
going to be more of an intermediate to
将更多地成为一个中间人
Advanced tutorial and that I'm not going
高级教程，我不会去
to be going over every single step in
每一步都要仔细检查
excruciating detail so if you're Vaguely
令人痛苦的细节，所以如果你含糊地
Familiar with how the tools work in
熟悉这些工具在中的工作方式
inkscape then you should be able to
Inkscape那么你应该能够
follow along with this tutorial
请按照本教程进行操作
otherwise sit back and enjoy what
否则就坐下来享受
inkscape can do
Inkscape可以做到
[Music]
[音乐]
so to get us started here in inkscape
为了让我们从Inkscape开始
let's start out by making sure we are
让我们从确保我们是
working with a similar layout by coming
通过以下方式使用类似的布局
up here to where it says View and having
在这里，它说的是查看和拥有
WID screen disabled now for some reason
由于某些原因，WID屏幕现已禁用
I think some of the newer versions of
我认为一些较新版本的
inkscape automatically start out in
Inkscape自动开始在
widescreen mode so if you have that
宽屏模式，所以如果你有
enabled just go ahead and disable that
启用只需继续并禁用该选项
and your layout should look the same as
并且您的布局看起来应该与
mine here on the screen so the first
我的在屏幕上，所以第一个
thing I'm going to do is I'm going to
我要做的是我要
create the shape or the emblem for the
创建形状或徽章
logo and I'm going to use the stars and
徽标和我要使用的星星和
polygons tool for that I'm going to use
为此，我将使用多边形工具
the polygon setting with all of these
具有所有这些功能的面设置
input values here and I'm going to click
在此处输入值，然后我将单击
and drag upward with my mouse on the
然后用我的鼠标在
canvas while holding control and shift
按住Ctrl和Shift键的同时使用画布
so I can get a six-sided shape like that
这样我就可以得到一个像那样的六边形
where the points go vertically up and
在那里这些点垂直向上
down as you can see there let me make
就像你看到的那样，让我来做
that a little
那有一点
larger okay I'm going to grab my
大一点，好的，我去拿我的
selection tool move this up towards the
选择工具将此向上移动到
center of the page a little more and I'm
页面的中心位置再靠中间一点，我就
going to convert this to a path by going
要将其转换为路径，方法是
to path object to path and then I'm
将对象路径到路径，然后我
going to grab the edit paths by nodes
要按节点抓取编辑路径
tool and I want to take these two nodes
工具和我想要获取这两个节点
right here and I'm going to enable the
就在这里，我将启用
transformation handles and I'm just
变形手柄，我只是
going to scale these nodes down a little
我要将这些节点缩小一点
bit like
有点像
that okay then I'm going to take these
好的，那么我要拿着这些
nodes over here and I'm going to scale
节点在这里，我要扩展
these down like that I'm holding control
这些就像那样，我控制着
and shift while I do this to lock the
在我这样做的同时按下Shift键以锁定
the uh aspect ratio and then I'm going
呃，长宽比，然后我要
to move these nodes up like that and now
将这些节点像这样向上移动，现在
we're starting to get the shape of our
我们开始有了我们的形状
emblem I may even pull this out a little
徽章我甚至可能会把它拉出来一点
bit you may have to tweak this a little
你可能需要稍微调整一下这个
bit just to get it how you like it that
只是为了得到你喜欢的样子
right there is about what I'm going for
这就是我想要的东西
so I'm going to leave it as it is
所以我要让它保持原样
I'm going to turn off my transformation
我要关掉我的变形
handles and then grab the selection tool
手柄，然后抓起选择工具
and let me open up the fill and stroke
让我打开填充物和笔触
menu which is located over here and I
菜单在这里，我在这里
will bring down the opacity of this a
将降低这一事件的不透明性
little bit so I could see through the
一点，这样我就能看穿
object as I'm working with it so what I
对象，因为我正在使用它，所以我
want to do now is round off the corners
现在想要做的是圆角
here and to make these Corners rounded
在这里，为了让这些角落变得圆润
I'm going to use a path effect for that
为此，我将使用路径效果
so I'll come up here to where it says
所以我会到上面写着的地方
path choose path effects click the plus
路径选择路径效果单击加号
icon down here to add new path effect
点击此处添加新的路径效果
and the path effect I am looking for is
而我正在寻找的路径效应是
Corners so I'm just going to type in
所以我要打字了
corners and there it is the corners path
拐角，这就是拐角小路
effect I'm going to grab the nodes tool
效果我要抓取节点工具
I'm going to click and drag over all of
我要单击并拖动所有
the nodes right here and I'm going to
这些节点就在这里，我要
pull down one of these green handles to
拉下这些绿色手柄中的一个
make these Corners rounded and you can't
把这些角变圆，你就不能
really see it happening as it happens
我真的看到了它的发生
probably not on my screen but if you see
可能不在我的屏幕上，但如果你看到
on your screen there should be a blue
在您的屏幕上应该有一个蓝色
outline indicating the degree to which
表明以下方面程度的大纲
the corners are being rounded right
边角正向右圆角
there and if you release the click you
在那里，如果你松开点击按钮
could see now we have some rounded
可以看到现在我们有一些圆形的
Corners there which is what I'm going
那里的角落，这就是我要去的地方
for now I want this top half of the the
现在我想要上半部分的比赛
design to be completely rounded so what
设计要完全圆润，那又如何？
I'm going to do is I'm going to deselect
我要做的是取消选择
these nodes and I'm going to take just
这些节点，我将只取
this node right here oops click the
这个节点就在这里，点击
wrong thing I'm going to take just this
错误的东西，我只想要这个
node right here and I'm going to bring
节点就在这里，我要把
this all the way down like that so we
像这样一直往下走，所以我们
end up with something like that right
最终会有这样的事情发生
there and now I will finalize this by
现在，我将通过以下方式完成这项工作
going to path object to path press one
转到路径对象到路径按一
to zoom back out to
要缩小到
100% and maybe even let me just make
100%，甚至可能让我做
this a little a little uh add a little
这个有点，呃，加一点
more vertical height to it like that
更垂直的高度，就像这样
this is just a personal preference I'm
这只是我的个人喜好
just eyeballing this as I go along okay
我只是边走边看，好吗？
that's looking good right there so now
看起来很不错，所以现在
I'm going to create some Mountains for
我要为你创造一些山脉
the background here to create the
此处的背景是创建
mountains I'm going to use the squares
高山，我要用广场
and rectangles tool I'm going to click
和矩形工具，我要点击
and drag I'm going to hold control and
拖拽我要保持控制和
shift while clicking and dragging to
在按住Shift键的同时单击并拖动
create a perfectly symmetrical square
创建一个完美对称的正方形
like that and I want to give this
就像这样，我想给你这个
rounded Corners a little bit I'm going
一点圆角，我要走了
to make these Corners a little rounded
让这些角落变得有点圆润
like that not much just a little bit and
就像这样，不是很多，只有一点点
then I will grab the selection tool and
然后我会抓起选择工具并
rotate this around like that I'm going
把这个像这样旋转，我要走了
to hold control while rotating so we get
在旋转时保持控制，这样我们就可以
it nice and vertical like that and I'm
它很漂亮，很垂直，我是
going to give this a different color
我要给这个换一种颜色
just so I could differentiate it up
这样我就能把它区分开来
against the emblem over here I'm going
在这里的徽章上我要走了
to duplicate this a few times to make
将这个复制几次，以使
some mountains in the background so I'm
背景中有几座山，所以我
going to press control D to duplicate
要按Ctrl D复制
I'll put this one up here control
我会把这个放在这里控制
duplicate again put this one down here
再复制一次，把这个放在这里
and then another copy over here and
然后在这里再复制一份，然后
that's about what I'm going for right
这就是我要做的正确的事情
there so I'm going to shift click all of
在这里，我要按Shift键，单击所有
these so I have them all
这些，所以我都有了
selected and I will unify them all Al
被选中，我将统一他们所有的Al
together by going to path
一起走上小路
Union and now I'm going to take a
联盟，现在我要带一个
duplicate of the emblem here I'm going
会徽的复制品，我要去
to select the emblem control D to
选择徽标控件D以
duplicate it hold shift click on this
复制它，按住Shift键，单击此按钮
shape and we're going to take the
形状，我们将采用
intersecting area here by going to path
通过转到PATH在此处相交区域
and selecting
和选择
intersection and now I'm going to add a
交叉点，现在我要添加一个
little bit of a uh a shadow effect to
有点呃阴影效果
the corners of these mountains here let
这些山的一角让这里
me grab the pen tool let me enable
我抓起钢笔工具让我启用
snapping and then I'm going to snap to
抓拍，然后我要抓拍
this corner right here to create a point
在这里的这个角上创建一个点
I'm going to hold control and bring this
我要控制住局面，把这个
line I'm going to bring this line down
我要把这条线拉下来
to the right to make sure it's parallel
向右，以确保它是平行的
with this line right here this angle of
这条线就在这里，这个角度
this mountain I'm going to bring it the
这座山我要带给它
opposite way like that then click and
像这样相反，然后点击并
I'll bring this one up here I'm letting
我会把这个拿上来，我正在出租
go of control at this point I'll bring
在这一点上失去控制，我会带来
this one up here click again and then
这个在这里，再点击一次，然后
back to the starting
回到起点
point okay so I had a little technical
好的，我有一点技术上的问题
difficulty there I had to redo that one
有困难，我不得不重做一次
okay let me grab a duplicate of this
好的，让我拿一份这个的复制品
copy now contrl D put this over here put
复制现在控制D把这个放在这里放
this one over here
这个就是这里
and there we go now I want to shift
好了，现在我想换个位子
click all of these to select them unify
单击所有这些选项以将其选中统一
them together path Union and then
他们一起走上联合之路，然后
subtract them from the mountains hold
把它们从高山上减去
shift click on the mountains path
按Shift键点击山间小路
difference and there we go that right
不同之处，我们就这样走吧
there is the effect I'm going for okay
这就是我想要的效果，好的
so now I'm going to create I'm going to
所以现在我要创造我要
create a little winding River to place
打造一条蜿蜒曲折的小河
right here in the Forefront of the uh
就在这里，呃，在最前线
design here so let me turn off snapping
在这里设计，让我关闭捕捉
first let me grab the pen tool and for
首先让我拿起钢笔工具，然后
this we're going to get a little
这是我们将要得到的一点
creative I'm going to create just one
有创意的我只会创造一个
vertical line like this I'm going to
像这样的垂直线，我要
click once to create a point hold
单击一次以创建点保持
control put this line down here like
控件将这条线放在这里，就像
that click again and press enter and
再次单击并按Enter键，然后
grab the nodes tool and give this line a
抓起结点工具并给这行一个
little bit of a curve I'm going to
我要做一个小小的曲折
select these handles over here and curve
在这里选择这些手柄，然后弯曲
this out like
这就像是
that there we go grab the selection tool
我们要去拿选择工具了
and duplicate this and I want to
复制这个，我想
position this in such a way that the
以这样的方式定位它，即
space between the two lines represents
两条线之间的空格表示
the shape kind of like a winding River
形状有点像一条蜿蜒的河流
now we're going to change the
现在我们要改变
perspective of this to make it look like
透视一下，让它看起来像
it's actually part of the landscape here
它实际上是这里风景的一部分
but for now we're just trying to get
但现在我们只是想要
this this shape right here between these
这个形状就在这两个之间
two lines and once you have that shape
两条线，一旦你有了这个形状
like that select both of them convert
就像选择他们两个人一样
these Strokes to a path path stroke to
这些笔划到路径路径笔划到
path and then unify them together go to
路径，然后将它们统一在一起，转到
path Union and now break them apart by
路径并集，现在通过以下方式将它们分开
going to path break apart and now if I
路要分开了，现在如果我
click off of that to deselect it you can
单击该选项可取消选择该选项
see this has been broken up into
看，这已经被分解成
separate pieces and I want this piece
分开，我想要这块
over here I'm G to press delete on the
在这里，我要按Delete键
keyboard to get rid of that and we're
键盘来摆脱它，我们正在
looking for this piece right here this
在这里寻找这件作品
is what we want to work with so let me
是我们想要合作的，所以让我
go back to my fill and stroke menu and
返回到我的填充和描边菜单
bring down the opacity of this a little
把这个的不透明度降低一点
bit so I can see it better I'm going to
这样我就能看得更清楚了，我要
place this over here and now I'm just
把这个放在这里，现在我只是
going to use the transformation handles
将使用变换句柄
to uh scale and Shear this as needed I'm
根据需要进行缩放和剪切，我是
just going to make this shorter like
我要把这段话缩短一点，就像
that maybe even scale this
甚至有可能达到这个规模
up like that there we
就这样，我们在那里
go maybe even make this a little wider
去吧，也许会把这个弄宽一点
so that it stretches out more across the
所以它会延伸到更多的
design okay that looks
设计不错，看起来不错
good and if you really want to sell this
很好，如果你真的想把这个卖了
effect you can use the perspective path
效果你可以使用透视路径
effects so let me come over here to the
所以让我到这里来看看
path effects menu let me add A New Path
路径效果菜单允许我添加新路径
effect and for this one I'm looking for
效果，对于这一次，我正在寻找
perspective envelope so I'm going to
透视封套，所以我要
type in PR RS and there it is
输入PR RS，它就在那里
perspective and now down here where it
透视图，现在在这里，它
says type make sure you have perspective
说类型要确保你有远见
enabled and I'm going to enable this one
已启用，我将启用此选项
right here that says mirror movements
就在这里，上面写着镜像运动
and vertical and now I can grab the
和垂直的，现在我可以抓住
nodes tool and I should be able to take
Nodes Tool和我应该能够
these two right here and bring this up
这两个人就在这里，把这个拿出来
like that and as you can see we're
就像你看到的那样，我们正在
changing the perspective of this River
改变这条河的视角
here to make it look like it's uh
让它看起来像是呃
disappearing into the vantage point
消失在有利位置
there now I'm going to convert that to a
现在，我将把它转换成一个
path by going to path object to path
通过转到路径对象到路径来进行路径
make that a little bit bigger so that it
把它弄大一点，这样它就
stretches Out Among the bottom of the
延伸到最底层的
design
设计
here and now I will fit that into the
现在，我将把它放入
emblem I may even make this a little bit
徽章我甚至可能会把这个做得有点
whoops I may even make this a little bit
哦，我甚至可能会把这件事做得有点
um wider like that I want the start of
嗯，像这样，我想要开始
this to be closer to this corner right
这个离这个拐角近一点，对吗？
here so that looks good as it is I'm
在这里，这样看起来很好，我是
going to leave that I'm going to take
我要走了，我要走了
this emblem shape right here control D
这里的这个徽章形状控制D
to duplicate it shift click the river
要复制它，请按住Shift键并单击河流
and go to path intersection and there we
然后走到小路交叉口，在那里我们
go now we have that right there okay so
去吧，我们就在那里，好的，所以
let's create a little pine tree to put
让我们造一棵小松树放在
right here in the Forefront of the
就在这里，在世界的最前沿
design to do that I'm going to grab the
为了做到这一点，我要抓住
squares and rectangles tool I want to
正方形和矩形工具我想
make make sure I have sharp
确保我有锐利的
Corners click and drag to create a
拐角单击并拖动以创建
square like that convert it to a path
像这样的正方形将其转换为路径
again make sure you have sharp Corners
再说一次，确保你有尖锐的角落
here path object to path grab the nodes
在这里，Path对象到Path抓取节点
tool I'm going to delete this node right
工具，我要删除这个节点
here by pressing delete on the keyboard
在这里，按键盘上的Delete键
and then I'll take these nodes over here
然后我把这些节点放在这里
and I'll make those Corners sharp like
我会让这些角落变得锋利
that and now I can grab the selection
现在我可以拿到选择了
tool and rotate this back around while
工具并将其旋转回来，同时
holding control so we lock it onto 15°
保持控制，以便我们将其锁定在15°
angles like that we want this nice and
像这样的角度，我们想要这个漂亮的
flat and upright and I'm just going to
平坦而笔直，我要
make this a little narrower I'll
把这个弄窄一点，我会
duplicate that bring this one down here
复制那个，把这个带到这里来
make this one a little
把这件做得小一点
bigger and then I'll duplicate that and
更大，然后我会复制它，然后
I'll bring this one down here and make
我会把这个拿下来，做一个
that one a little bigger like that I
像那样大一点的那个我
should probably be using darker colors
可能应该用更深的颜色
so you can see this better let me go
这样你就能看得更清楚了让我走吧
with blue there we
蓝色在那里，我们
go and there we go I think that right
去吧，我们去吧，我想这是对的
there looks good so I'm going to use
看起来不错，所以我要用
that as it is I'm going to select all of
鉴于此，我将选择所有
those path Union and there we go there's
那些小路联合，我们去那里，那里
our tree so let me scale this down and
我们的树，所以让我把它缩小
place this at the front of the design
把这个放在设计的前面
over
完毕
here I may even place
在这里，我甚至可以把
this I think right about here would be
我想这里应该是
good I want this to be I want the tip of
很好，我想要这个，我想要小费
this tree to go to the the edge of the
这棵树走到了边缘
river right here whoops what happened
河水就在这里，发生了什么事？
okay there we
好的，我们到了
go I'm going to place that right about
去吧，我要把它放在
there okay that's good enough so let me
好了，够了，让我来吧
duplicate the emblem and take the
复制会徽，并将
intersecting area there
那里的交叉区
intersection and let me give this thing
交叉口，让我把这个东西
some color so we could start
一些颜色，这样我们就可以开始
differentiating the elements here let me
区分这里的元素让我
select everything we can now bring the
选择我们现在可以带来的一切
opacity up and start adding in some
增加不透明度并开始添加一些
color so I want the mountain range here
所以我想要这里的山脉
to be a dark shade of blue actually I'm
成为一种深蓝色实际上我是
want to start with the background here I
我想从这里的背景开始
want the background to be a light shade
我希望背景是浅色的
of blue I'm going to start with uh that
蓝色的，我将从呃那个开始
shade right there maybe that and then
就在那里遮阳，也许是那个，然后
I'll take this and I'll make this a dark
我要这个，我要调成深色的
blue like that and I want the tree to be
像这样的蓝色，我希望这棵树是
that same dark shade of blue so I'm
同样的深蓝色，所以我
going to grab the dropper tool which is
我要拿起滴管工具，它是
located over here I just like to use the
位于这里，我只是喜欢使用
letter d on the keyboard D for dropper
键盘D上的字母d表示滴管
it's easy to remember and there you go
它很容易记住，然后你就可以了
and S for selection back to the
和S的选拔回到了
selection tool grab the uh the river
选择工具抓取呃河流
here I'm going to make this the same
在这里，我要把它变成同样的东西
color as this right here D for the
颜色就像这里的D代表
dropper s for selection there we go and
投手S入选，我们开始吧
now I'm going to place us a sun a little
现在我要给我们放一个小太阳
bit of uh sunrays in the background here
这里的背景中有一些呃阳光
so let me grab these circles and
所以让我抓起这些圆圈
ellipses tool click and drag to create a
椭圆工具单击并拖动以创建
perfectly round circle like that place
像那个地方一样完美的圆形
it in the center of the design I'm going
我要把它放在设计的中心
to make this white so we can see it
把它变成白色，这样我们就能看到它了
better and that's actually the color I'm
更好，那实际上是我想要的颜色
going to use for the Sun so let me
要用来晒太阳，所以让我来
Center this up I'm going to shift click
将这个居中，我要Shift，点击
both of these open up the aligned
这两者都打开了对齐的
distribute menu which is over here we
分发菜单，菜单在我们这边
can press control shift and to access
可以按Ctrl Shift并访问
that and from the relative two I want
再加上我想要的两个亲戚
last selected chosen I'm just going to
最后一次选择我只是要
Center that up on the vertical axis like
在垂直轴上居中，就像
that now let me make this a little bit
现在让我把这一点说成是
bigger and I'm going to lower this down
更大的，我要把这个放下来
beneath the mountains now you can lower
在群山之下，你现在可以低下
you can raise and lower objects using
您可以使用以下命令升高和降低对象
these buttons I just like to use the
这些按钮我只是喜欢用
page up and page down keys on the
上的Page Up和Page Down键
keyboard so I'm going to press page down
键盘，我要按PAGE DOWN
to lower that there we go and now I'm
去降低我们要去的地方，现在我
going to make a duplicate copy of this
我要把这个复制一份
I'm going to press controll D I'm going
我要按控制键D，我要走了
to make this one
做这件事
bigger there here we go and I'm going to
更大的，我们要去，我要去
make this one a lighter shade of blue
把这个改成浅一点的蓝色
again pressing D on the keyboard to grab
再次按键盘上的D键抓取
the dropper grab the uh fill and stroke
滴管抓住，呃，填充和划水
menu make this one a lot lighter oops
菜单让这道菜清淡了很多。
and then I'll just take this and page
然后我就拿着这个翻页
down and lower it beneath like that and
像这样往下压，往下放，然后
I'll maybe even make that one a little
我甚至可能会把那个做得有点
darker okay there we go now I'm going to
好了，我们走吧，现在我要去
duplicate this circle again controll D
再次复制此圆控制D
I'll make this one a little
我要把这件做得小一点
darker maybe even add a little more blue
更深的颜色甚至会增加一点蓝色
into it like that and I'll make this
就像这样，我会做这个
larger and I'm going to lower this down
再大一点，我要把这个放低一点
by pressing page the the page down key
按Page键，然后按Page Down键
like
喜欢
that there we go I'm going to make this
我们走吧，我要做这件事
about this big and then I'll make this
大概这么大，然后我就做这个
one about this
关于这件事的一个
big and at this point we're just trying
在这一点上我们只是想试着
to size things up to make sure it fits
给东西打量尺寸以确保合身
nicely and then I'm going to make this
很好，然后我要做这个
emblem I want this to be a darker shade
徽章我想要一个更深的色调
of blue than this so let me press D on
比这更蓝，所以让我按D键
the keyboard to grab the dropper and
抓取滴管的键盘和
I'll make this one a little darker
我会把这件做深一点
okay that looks better now I'm going to
好的，现在看起来好多了，我要
update the river color to match this
更新河流颜色以匹配此颜色
shade of blue right here so let me just
蓝色的阴影就在这里，所以让我
grab the dropper and do that and now I'm
抓住滴管，然后这样做，现在我
going to take the intersecting area of
要取的相交区域
this circle right here so let me grab
这个圆圈就在这里，让我抓住
the emblem and duplicate that shift
徽章和复制移位
click the circle path
单击圆形路径
intersection there we go and as you can
我们走到十字路口，尽你所能
see the design is coming together here
看，设计在这里汇聚在一起
the one final last step would be to add
最后一步是添加
a little bit of a white border going
有一点白色边框
around the outside and a drop shadow
在外面和一个阴影周围
beneath it so it really pops off the
在它下面，所以它真的从
page so to do that let me select just
要这样做，请让我只选择
the emblem right here and go to path and
会徽就在这里，然后转到Path和
choose uh linked
选择呃链接的
offset and I want to make this offset a
偏移量，我想将此偏移量设置为
totally different color so we can see it
完全不同的颜色，所以我们可以看到它
better I'm going to choose red I'm going
我还是选红色好了，我要走了
to grab the node tool and there should
要抓取节点工具，应该有
be this little node up top over here and
是这上面的这个小节点，然后
you should be able to grab this and pull
你应该能够抓住这个，然后拉
this out like that and I want the border
就像这样，我想要边界
of this emblem to be about about that
这个会徽大概是关于那个的
big I can finalize that by going to path
大我可以通过转到Path来完成这一点
object to path and then I will make that
对象到路径，然后我会将其
white grab the selection tool and now
白色抓起选择工具，现在
I'm going to duplicate that by pressing
我要重复这一点，按下
control D and I'm going to make this one
CONTROL D和我要做这个
black and now I can use my page down key
黑色，现在我可以使用我的Page Down键
to lower that down and then I can use my
把它放下来，然后我就可以用我的
arrow keys to bring this down a little
箭头键把这个稍微调低一点
bit there we go I'll give that a blur
我们走吧，我会让它变得模糊
and I'll bring down the opacity of that
我会把它的不透明性降下来
blur like that and now I'll have to
像这样模糊，现在我不得不
deselect it and select it again and now
取消选择它，然后再次选择它
I can use my arrow keys to move that
我可以用我的箭头键移动它
down a little bit just to give a little
稍微往下一点，就是为了给一点
bit of
比特
offset okay there we go and I think that
补偿，好的，我们开始了，我想
should do it for this lesson that is how
为了这一课应该这样做，这就是为什么
you can go about creating a mountain
你可以着手建造一座山
range logo with a winding River and a
带有蜿蜒的河流和
pine tree and a rising sun coming up
松树和冉冉升起的太阳
beneath it inside of this element using
在该元素内部的它下面使用
nothing but simple shapes in inkscape
Inkscape中只有简单的形状
before I end this video if you found
在我结束这段视频之前，如果你找到
this lesson useful then consider
这一课很有用，然后考虑
checking out my inkscape master class
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over all of the tools and
在那里我检查了所有的工具和
features in inkscape and I explain what
Inkscape中的功能，我将向您解释
they are and Demon demonstrate how they
他们和恶魔展示了他们是如何
work kind of like how I did in this
就像我在这件事上做的那样
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
您可以在那里提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
随时从我这里收到，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
没有每月会员费
just pay $17 one time and you're in for
只需一次支付17美元，您就能获得
Life I'll have some information about
生活我会有一些信息
that in the description of the video if
在视频的描述中，
you want to check that out as always
您想一如既往地检查一下
thanks for watching
感谢收看